PRODUCT DESIGNER



# **ABOUT ME**

I am a skilled product designer and graphic web designer with expertise in Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Xd, Figma, HTML/CSS, TAILWIND, and JavaScript, as well as understanding of Fronted development skills. I have a Bachelor's degree in Information Technology and strong design capabilities.



### CONTACT

Address:

Avenue 7 Kn 134 St

Mobile: 0788393331

Email:

jonakaisa@gmail.com

Skype:

Jonathan Kalisa



#### **SKILLS**

**UI/UX DESIGN** 

FRONTED DEVELOPMENT

**CMS DEVELOPMENT** 

**ADOBE SUITE** 



**ENGLISH** 

**FRENCH** 

**SWAHILL** 





# **EXPERIENCES**

CREAXION-TBWA

PRODUCT DESIGN-FRONTEND DEV

2018-2021

Creative problem-solver with excellent design skills. Collaborative and dedicated to delivering high-quality work for clients at

Creaxion-Rwanda

ZATEC

PRODUCT DESIGNER

2021 - 2023

Expertise in product design and strong remote collaboration skills demonstrated in role at Zatec, contributing to successful projects for

external clients in Germany.

ALIGHT AMERICAN RFC

SR CODING OFFICER & PRODUCT DESIGNER

2023-

Leadership and technical skills demonstrated in role as head of refugee coding program at Alight, empowering marginalized

communities through education.



# **EDUCATION**

ADVENTIST UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL AFRICA

2015 - 2019

**BACHELOR DEGREE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY** 

I have a Bachelor's degree in Information Technology from Adventist University of Central Africa, with a strong foundation of knowledge

and skills in the field of IT.



#### REFERENCE

#### JACQUE PREVERT RUMANYIKA

Coordinator, ALIGHT RWANDA Phone: +250 788 383 393

Email: Jacques-PrevertR@WEAREALIGHT.ORG

**MUTANGANA AFRODICE** 

COO DIGITAL AFRICA Phone: +250 788 306 293 Email: amutangana@klab.rw



#### **PORTFOLIO LINKS**

- https://www.behance.net/jonathankalisa
- https://kalisa.netlify.app/



# **DECLARATION**

I, the undersigned, certify that the information above correctly describes my qualifications and experience.

Kalisa Jonathan

